邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
爸爸
Dad.
萨姆 这次比你以前遇到的都要麻烦 它们无处不在
Sam This is bigger than you think. They're everywhere.
我想他想我们继续他的事业
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
拯救人类 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people. Hunting things. The family business.
我真不能理解你对他的盲目信任
I don't understand the blind faith you have in the man.
你他妈的是个混蛋 知道吗？
You're a selfish bastard, you know that?
你只是做你自己想做的 而不管别人
You just do whatever you want.
我就要开车了 你会被抛弃在这 听到没？
Hey, I'm taking off. I will leave your ass, you hear me?
这正是我想要你做的
That's what I want you to do.
我是梅格
l'm Meg.
我叫萨姆
Sam.
那么你将出发去哪里呢？
So where you headed?
- 我不会告诉你的 - 为什么不？
- No way l'm telling you. - Why not?
你可能是个变态
You could be some kind of freak.
这可没道理
It makes no sense.
我把他们都抓住 怎么样？
Hell, I could've taken them both.
为什么让他们走掉？
Why let them go?
（芝加哥 伊利诺斯州）
太好了
Great.
喂
Hello.
系统启动
System disarmed.
系统锁定
System armed.
你好梅雷迪思 我是克里斯汀 你一定得和我说说昨天的事
Hey, Meredith, it's Kristen. You have to tell me what happened last night.
记得回电
Call me.
嘿 梅雷迪思 我是德里克 你去哪里了？
Hey, Meredith. It's Derrick. Where you been?
我一整天都在找你
I've tried to get you all day.
我有些有意思的东西给你看
cause I got maybe something's gonna pleseyou.
猜猜是什么 到家后给我回电
Guess what.Call mewhen you come back, ok.
想知道答案的话 给我电话
lf you wanna solve that mystery, call me.
好吗？再见
All right? bye.
嘿 梅雷迪思
Hey, Meredith.
听着 别说我没挺你
Listen, don't say I don't got your back.
我知道上次那家伙伤透了你的心 不过这次这个
I know that guy ripped your heart out last time, but this one…
《邪恶力量》
（一周后）
好了 迪恩
All right, Dean.
这就是那个地方
This is the place.
我和老爸没有那些愚蠢的持卡人 也能利用信用卡
I gotta say Dad and me did just fine without these stupid costumes.
我感觉自己像个戏剧学院的学生
I feel like a high school drama dork.
你演出那场叫什么来着？
What was that play that you did? That.
表演的不错 你也很可爱
What was it? Our Town.
听着 你到底有完没完？
You wanna pull this off, or not?
我只是想说开支很大
I'm saying these outfits cost hard earned money, okay?
谁的开支？
Whose?
我们的
Ours.
你以为盗用信用卡很简单？
You think credit card fraud's easy?
谢谢你让我们进来
Thanks for letting us look around.
警察说他们已经检查了这个地方 所以
Well, police said they were done with the place, so…
你们是那个报警器公司的？
You guys said you're with the alarm company?
是的
That's right.
无意冒犯 但你们的报警器真没什么作用
Well, no offense, but your alarm's about as useful as boobs on a man.
这就是我们来的原因
Well, that's why we're here.
看看为什么不起作用 防止此类事件再次发生
See what went wrong, stop it from happening again.
大妈 你发现的尸体？
Now, madam, you found the body?
是的
Yeah.
是刚刚发生惨案后吗？
Right after it happened.
不 过了些日子
No. Few days later.
梅雷迪思的老板打来电话 她没来上班
Meredith's work called, she hadn't showed up.
我来敲她的门
I knocked on her door.
那个时候我发现很难闻的气味
That's when I noticed the smell.
有打开的窗吗 搏斗的痕迹呢？
Any windows open? Any sign of break in?
窗户都紧闭着 门也是插上的
No, windows were locked. Door was bolted.
锁链还在门上呢 为了进来 我还把它切断了
Chain was on the door. We had to cut it.
报警器还开着吗？
And the alarm was still on?
就像我抱怨的 你公司的东西真的不怎么样
Like I said bang up job your company's doing.
你有没有看到翻倒的家具 打破的玻璃 搏斗的痕迹？
You see any overturned furniture? Broken glass? Struggle?
所有的东西都完好… 除了梅雷迪思
Everything was in perfect condition. Except Meredith.
梅雷迪思 她怎么了呢？
And what condition was Meredith in?
梅雷迪思被撕碎了 满地都是
Meredith was all over. In pieces.
杀害她的凶手一定充满力量
The guy who killed her must have been a wack job.
但是我想说 如果不是这样
But, I'll tell you, if I didn't know any better,
那就一定是野生动物所为
I'd have said a wild animal did it.
大妈 你介意我们花点时间 再把这个地方做个彻底检查？
Madam, you mind if we take some time, give this place a once over?
请便
Go right ahead.
出去的时候锁上门
Knock yourself out.
这个凶手出入了这间房子 没有武器 没有指纹 什么都没有
So the killer walks in and out of the apartment. No weapons, no prints.
说实话 当我看到报道的时候
I'm telling you the minute I found that article.
我就知道这是我们该解决的
I knew this was our kind of gig.
我同意
I think I agree with you.
你和警察谈过了？
You say you talked to the cops?
是的 我和艾米谈过了
Uh, yeah. Spoke to Amy.
一个迷人的警察
A charming, perky officer of the law.
你查到些什么？
Yeah? What did you find out?
她属人马座的
Well, she's a Sagittarius.
她喜欢龙舌兰酒 我是指
She loves tequila. I mean…
她还有些小的纹身图案
Oh, and she's got this tattoo, right.
迪恩
Dean.
什么
What?
是的 没有什么新的情况
Yeah. Nothing we don't already know.
除了他们没有报道在报纸上的
Except for one thing they're keeping out of the papers.
梅雷迪思的心脏被挖走了
Meredith's heart was missing.
她的心？
Her heart?
是的 她的心
Yeah, her heart.
你觉得是什么东西干的？
So, what do you think did it?
房东太太说像是动物的袭击
The landlady said it looked like an animal attack.
也许就是那样
Maybe it was.
人狼？
Werewolf?
不是 月的轨道不符合
Not a werewolf.The lunar cycle's not right.
如果它是个生物 就一定会留下痕迹
Plus, if it was a creature, it would've left some kind of trace.
一定是个鬼魂
It's probably a spirit.
帮我找找看有没有黑胶带
See if you can find any masking tape around.
以前看到过这个符号吗？
Ever see that symbol before?
没有
Never.
我也是
Me neither.
真的？你做体操运动员五年了吗
Really? You were a gymnast for five years?
- 来酒吧帮帮忙 - 太棒了
- Help here at the bar. - Awesome.
谢谢
Thanks.
我和吧台的招待谈过了
Talked to the bartender.
除了她的电话 你还得到些什么？
You get anything?Besides her number.
兄弟 我可是专业人士 你可不能那么说我…
Dude. I'm a professional. I'm offended that you would think that.
好吧
All right.
你能不能用用你的大脑 迪恩？
You mind doing a little bit of thinking with your upstairs brain, Dean?
这里也没什么可查
Huh? There's nothing.
梅雷迪思在这里工作 她是个招待而已
Meredith worked here. She waited tables.
所有的人都是她的朋友 别人也说她很正常
Everyone here is her friend. They say she's normal.
死前她也没说过什么古怪的话
She didn't do or say anything weird before she died. So…
那个符号呢？你查到些什么？
What about that symbol? Anything?
什么也没有
Nothing.
爸爸的日记 一般的书本上都没有
It wasn't in Dad's journal or any of the usual books.
我想 我得花点工夫了
So l'll just have to dig a little deeper, I guess.
在梅雷迪思之前 第一个牺牲者情况呢？
There was a victim before Meredith?
好吧 他的名字
Right, yeah. His name was…
名字是本·斯沃斯托姆
His name was Ben Swardstrom.
上个月他在家里发现被杀害
He was mutilated. Same deal.
同样的情况 门被锁上了 警报器还开着
The door was locked, the alarm was on.
这两者有联系吗？
ls there any connection between them?
现在还没发现
Nothing I can tell. I mean, not yet.
本是个银行人士 梅雷迪思是个女招待
Ben was a banker, Meredith was a waitress.
他们没见过对方 是两个来自不同世界的人
They never met, never knew anyone in common. From different worlds.
看来我们唯一成功的就是
So the only successful intel we've scored so far.
我拿到了吧台招待的电话
is the bartender's phone number.
什么？
What?
萨姆
Sam.
梅格
Meg.
萨姆
Sam.
萨姆 是你吗 天啊
Sam, is that you? Oh, my gosh.
你在这里干吗？
What are you doing here?
我刚到这里 拜访朋友
I'm just in town visiting friends.
你朋友在哪儿？
Where are they?
他们不在这里 那么你呢
Well, they're not here right now. But what about you.
梅格 我还以为你去了加州
Meg. You were going to California.
哦 我去了
I did.
去过 看过 征服过
l came, I saw, I conquered.
我刚和那个什么家伙
Oh, and I met what's his name.
叫麦克或莫里什么的 在这个吧里聊天
Something Michael Murray, at a bar.
谁？
Who?
别管
It doesn't matter.
而且也有点厌倦了 所以我在这里住一段时间
Anyway, the whole scene got old. So l'm living here for a while.
你从芝加哥来吗？
You're from Chicago?
不是 是麻省 到这里结束
No. Massachusetts. Andover.
天啊 萨姆
Gosh, Sam.
我们又见面 这一切太神奇了？
What are the odds we'd run into each other?
我也觉得 我还以为再也见不到你呢
Yeah, I know. I thought I'd never see you again.
我很高兴你错了
Well, l'm glad you were wrong.
伙计 咳嗽时捂着嘴 好吗
Dude. Cover your mouth.
不好意思 梅格
Yeah, l'm sorry, Meg.
这是 这是我哥哥迪恩
This is… This is my brother, Dean.
他就是迪恩？
This is Dean?
是的 你听说过我？
Yeah. So you've heard of me?
是的 我当然听说过你
Oh, yeah. I've heard of you.
很好 你对你弟弟就像对行李一样
Nice, the way you treat your brother like luggage.
什么？
Sorry?
你为什么不让他去做他喜欢的事？
Let him do what he wants to do.
别再老拽着他不放好吗
Stop dragging him over God's green earth.
梅格 现在没事了
Meg. It's all right.
挺尴尬的
Okay. Awkward.
我去喝点东西
I'm gonna get a drink now.
萨姆 对不起
Sam, l'm sorry.
只是想起他以前怎么对你
It's just the way you told me he treats you…
如果换了是我 我会杀了他
lf it were me, l'd kill him.
现在没事了 他没什么恶意
It's all right. He means well.
你还在城里的时候 我们该聚聚
We should hook up while you're in town.
是的
Yeah.
我要带你到处逛逛
Show you a hell of a time.
听起来不错 不如你把电话给我？
That's great. Why don't you give me your number.
312- 555- 0143
312-555-0143.
我从不知道你的姓
You know, I never got your last name.
马斯特斯
Masters.
人格担保
Scout's honor.
我希望能再看到你 萨姆
I hope to see you around, Sam.
她到底是谁？
Who the hell was she?
我也不太清楚 只见过她一次而已
I don't really know. I only met her once.
和她再次相见？
Meeting up with her again…
我不知道 兄弟 这太奇怪了
I don't know, man, it's weird.
她刚才说什么 我把你当行李？
Well, what was she saying? I treat you like luggage?
你当着这个婊子说我坏话？
What, were you bitching about me to a chick?
听着 我很抱歉 迪恩
Look. I'm sorry. Dean.
那次我们吵的很厉害
It was when we had that fight when I was in that bus stop in Indiana.
是印地安那停车站的那次
It's not important.
她说的是真的吗？我让你违背自己的意愿了 萨姆？
Any truth to it? Am I keeping you against your will?
不 当然不是 你能不能听我说？
No, of course not. Now, would you listen?
什么
What?
我觉得这里面有古怪 迪恩
There's something strange going on.
那就和我说说看 我没把她当回事
Tell me about it. She wasn't that into me.
不 兄弟 我是指就像所有奇怪的事情一样
No, man. I mean our kind of strange.
也许这是个线索
Maybe even a lead.
为什么那么说？
Why do you say that?
几星期前我在路边遇到了梅格
l met Meg weeks ago on the side of the road.
现在我却在一个芝加哥的酒吧见到她
Now I run into her in some Chicago bar?
同一个酒吧 而这里的一个招待被某种鬼魂杀害
The bar where a waitress was slaughtered by something supernatural.
- 你认为这很奇怪吗？- 经常会这样
- Think that's weird? - Coincidence. It happens.
是的 是经常发生 可不会在我们身上
Well, yeah, it happens. But not to us.
听着 也许我会弄错
I could be wrong.
可我觉得有些古怪令我不能平常的对待这个女孩
, but there's something about her. That I can't quite put my finger on.
可我打赌你想那么做
l bet you'd like to.
也许她并不是嫌疑犯
Maybe she's not a suspect.
也许你想和她有点什么
You got a thing for her, huh?
也许你用脑子过分了吧
Maybe you're thinking a little too much with the upstairs brain. Huh?
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
帮我查查是否有个梅格·马斯特斯从麻省来
Check if there's really a Meg Masters from Andover.
也查查关于那个符号
. See if you can dig anything up on that symbol on Meredith's floor.
那你去做什么？
What are you gonna do?
我去监视梅格
l'm gonna watch Meg.
我想看看究竟
l wanna see what's what.
好吧 你有点反常哦
Better safe. You little pervert. Dude.
走了 我走了
l'm going, l'm going.
- 嘿 - 你正潜伏在那个女孩的住所外面 是吗？
- Hey. - You're lurking outside her apartment?
不是
No.
是的
Yes.
你的反应真有意思
Funny way of showing your affection.
你找到关于她的资料没？
You find anything on her or what?
她检查了 这里电话本上有位梅格·马斯特斯
She checks out. There's a Masters in the phone book.
我甚至查到了她的高中照片
I pulled up her high school photo.
听着 你为什么不去敲她的门
Why don't you go knock on her door…
和她来段浪漫的诗歌阅读呢 或着做点其它什么？
and invite her to a poetry reading or whatever it is you do?
那个符号呢？找到些什么吗？
What about the symbol? Any luck?
是的 这次我运气不错 好象是和索罗亚斯德教有关
I did have some luck. It's… Turns out it's Zoroastrian.
非常古老的教派 还远在基督诞生前2000多年
Very, very old school, like 2000 years before Christ.
是个关于恶魔daeva的符号
It's a sigil for a Daeva.
什么是daeva？
What's a Daeva?
翻译过来就是「暗黑魔王」
Translates to "demon of darkness."
索罗亚斯德教描述的魔鬼 凶残兽性
Zoroastrian demons. And they're savage, animalistic.
令人厌恶的 就跟比特斗犬一样凶狠
You know, nasty attitudes. Kind of like demonic pit bulls.
你怎么查到的呢？
How'd you figure that out?
- 我的信用 你不用像我呆在一堆书里搜索这一切 - 是吗
- Give me credit.l can chase paper too. - Oh, yeah?
告诉我你查的最后一本书的名字
Name the last book you read.
我和爸爸的朋克莱博通电话 是他告诉我这些的
I called Caleb, he told me, all right?
而且还有些事情 这些daeva是被召唤的
Yeah. Here's the thing, Daevas they have to be summoned, conjured.
所以有人在操纵它们？
So someone's controlling it?
是的 正是这个意思
Yeah, that's what l'm saying.
从我查到的资料来看 这也是比较危险的事情
From what I gather, it's pretty risky too.
这些鬼魂会吃掉手…
They tend to bite the hand that feeds them.
胳膊 甚至 躯干
And the arms and torsos.
那它们是什么样子？
So, what do they look like?
从来没有人看到过它们
Nobody's seen them for a couple of millennia.
能召唤那么古老的鬼魂
Summoning a demon that ancient.
一定有人完全了解那些古老的东西
Someone really knows their stuff.
我认为这里有个很厉害的对手
I think we got a major player in town.
你为什么不上去和她亲热还在这里干吗？
Why don't you give that girl a private stripogram.
你咬我啊
Bite me.
是你去咬她
Bite her.
可别留下齿印哦
Don't leave teeth marks. Just enough to where.
萨姆 还在吗
Sam? You.
不 不 我只是
No, no. I'm-l'm just.
变态
Pervert.
[咒语]
[CHANTING lN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
我觉得你还不应该来
I don't think you should come.
因为那对兄弟还在镇上
Because the brothers, they're in town.
我不知道
l didn't know that.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
是的 我会在这里 等着你
Yes. l'll be here waiting for you.
这究竟是什么鬼玩意？
What the hell?
伙计 我有话和你说
Dude, I gotta talk to you.
所以 那么美女梅格是召唤daeva的人？
So hot little Meg is summoning the Daeva?
看起来 她好象在用一个黑色的祭坛在控制它们
Looks like she was using that black altar to control the thing.
看来萨姆的感觉是对的哦
So Sammy's got a thing for the bad girl?
和哪个碗有什么关系呢？
What's the deal with that bowl?
她在和碗说话
She talked into it.
就象女巫和水晶球对话
the way witches used to scry into crystal balls or entrails.
她在和某人交流
She was communicating.
和daeva吗？
With the Daeva?
不 你说那些东西是无意识的
No. You said those things were savages.
是其它的什么人
No, this was someone different.
给她指令的人
Someone who's giving her orders.
即将到达那个仓库的人
Someone…who's coming to that warehouse.
太糟糕了
Holy crap.
什么？
What?
本来想和你早点说的
What I was gonna tell you earlier.
警察局的朋友艾米的确帮了我大忙
I pulled a favor with my friend Amy over at the police department.
两个死者的完全的资料
The complete records of the two victims.
我们刚开始遗漏了某些东西
We missed something the first time.
什么？
What?
第一个死者 这个老人？
The first victim, the old man.
他从没离开过芝加哥
He spent his whole life in Chicago…
除了他的出生
but he wasn't born here.Look where he was born.
堪萨斯州 劳伦斯
Lawrence, Kansas.
梅雷迪思 第2个死者？
And Meredith, the second victim?
她是被领养的
Turns out she was adopted.
猜猜看她是从那里来的？
Guess where she's from.
堪萨斯州 劳伦斯
Lawrence, Kansas.
太糟糕了
Holy crap.
是的
Yeah.
我是指 那是恶魔杀害妈妈的地方
It is where the demon killed Mom.
也是所有事情的开端
It's where everything started.
你觉得梅格和那个魔鬼有关系？
You think Meg's tied up with the demon?
我觉得这很有可能
It's a definite possibility.
那和劳伦斯有何关联呢？
What's the significance of Lawrence?
那些daeva又是怎么被召唤的呢？
And how do these Daeva things fit in?
听我的
Beats me.
我说我们去毁了那个黑色祭坛 抓住梅格好好的审问她一番
I say we trash that black altar, grab Meg and have an interrogation.
不 不行 我们得暗中行事
No. We can't. We shouldn't tip her off.
我们要偷偷溜进那个仓库
We gotta stake out that warehouse.
我们去看看到底她要和什么东西见面
We gotta see who…or what is showing up to meet her.
我要说一句
l'll tell you one thing…
我觉得我们两不该单独行动
l don't think we should do this alone.
我们发现了杀害妈妈的重要线索
We think we got a serious lead on the thing that killed Mom.
是个仓库 西1435号
So… This warehouse, it's 1435 West Erie.
爸爸 收到消息后
Dad, if you get this.
尽快赶来芝加哥
Get to Chicago as soon as you can.
留言？
Voice mail?
是的
Yeah.
天 你拿了些什么来？
Jeez. What'd you get?
我几乎把车上的东西都拿来了
I ransacked that trunk.
圣水 我能想到的武器
Holy water, every weapon that I could think of.
针对半打不同宗教的驱魔卷轴
Exorcism rituals from about a half dozen religions.
我不知道会面对什么
I'm not sure what to expect.
所以我觉得我们该做好各种准备
so I guess we should just expect everything, huh?
今晚不一般哦
Big night.
是的
Yeah.
你紧张？
Nervous?
不 你呢？
No. No. Are you?
不 一点也不
No. No way.
天啊 你能想象我们要是真找对了那个恶魔
Could you imagine if we actually found that damn thing? That demon?
别想这么多好吗？
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
我知道 我只是说 如果真是那样呢？
l know. l'm just saying what if we did?
如果所有的事真的就在这个晚上结束呢？
What if this whole thing was over tonight?
兄弟 我要睡一个星期
Man, l'd sleep for a month.
回到学校 重新做人
Go back to school. Just be a person again.
你想重新回到学校？
You wanna go back to school?
是的 当我们杀了那个恶魔
Yeah, once we're done hunting it.
怎么了 那样不对吗？
ls there something wrong with that?
不 那样很好 对你来说很好
No. No. It's great. Good for you.
当这一切都结束 你会去做什么？
I mean… What are you gonna do when it's over?
永远都不会结束
It's never gonna be over.
还会有其它的鬼怪事件发生
There's gonna be others. There's gonna be something to hunt.
总有什么东西等着你去猎杀 可你自己总有为自己考虑吧
There's gotta be something you want for yourself.
我不想你一结束就马上离开 萨姆
Yeah, I don't want you to leave the second this thing's over, Sam.
伙计 你怎么了？
Dude, what's your problem?
为什么你认为是我拉着你到处跑
Why do you think I drag you everywhere? Huh?
你想想是什么原因让我来斯坦福找你呢？
Why do you think I came and got you at Stanford?
因为爸爸遇到了麻烦
Because Dad was in trouble.
因为你想找到杀害妈妈的恶魔
You wanted to find what killed Mom.
是的 是那样 可不止那些原因 兄弟
Yes, that, but it's more than that, man.
你和我还有爸爸
You and me and Dad.
我想我们又重新在一起生活
I mean, I want us to be together again.
我想我们重新开始一个家
I want us to be a family again.
迪恩 我们是一家人
Dean, we are a family.
我会为了你做任何事
I'd do anything for you.
但有些事情是回不去的
But things will never be the way they were before.
不 能回去
Could be.
可我不想他们回到最初
I don't want them to be.
我不会这样过一辈子
I'm not gonna live this life forever.
迪恩 当这一切都结束
Dean, when this is all over…
你得让我走自己的路
you're gonna have to let me go my own way.
[咒语]
[CHANTING lN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
伙计们 干吗躲躲藏藏象孩子样 不是吗？
Guys. Hiding's a little bit childish, don't you think?
这没有逃出我的计划
Well, that didn't work out like l'd planned.
为什么不出来呢？
Why don't you come out.
萨姆 我必须得说 这对我们的友谊来说是欺骗
Sam…l have to say, this puts a real crimp in our relationship.
是的 告诉我关于那个恶魔的事
Yeah, tell me about it.
你那些daeva朋友呢？
So where's your little Daeva friend?
就在周围
Around.
你的那些枪一点用也没有
The shotgun's not gonna do much good.
哦 别担心 甜心
Well, don't worry, sweetheart.
枪可不是用来对付daeva的
Shotgun's not for the demon.
它是谁 梅格？谁要来这里？
So who is it, Meg? Who's coming?
你在等谁？
Who are you waiting for?
你
You.
萨姆 别再犯这样的错了 你这位女朋友是个婊子
Hey, Sam? Don't take this the wrong way, but your girlfriend is a bitch.
这所有的一切都是个圈套
This…The whole thing was a trap.
在酒吧和你遇见
Running into you at the bar.
跟踪你到这里 偷听你的对话
Following you here hearing what you had to say.
这都是设计好的 不是吗？
It was all a setup, wasn't it?
所有的死者都是来自劳伦斯
That the victims were from Lawrence?
那并不意味着什么
Doesn't mean anything.
只是为了吸引你 就是那样
lt was just to draw you in.
你毫无理由就杀了那两个人
You killed those two people for nothing.
宝贝 我杀过的人多了
Baby, l've killed a lot more for a lot less.
你设圈套给我们 干得不错
You trapped us. Good for you.
现在任你宰割
It's Miller time.
为什么现在还不动手啊？
Why don't you kill us already?
没必要这样着急吧 不是吗？
Not very quick on the uptake, are we?
陷阱又不是为你设的
This trap isn't for you.
爸爸
Dad.
他们是给爸爸设的圈套
It's a trap for Dad.
哦 甜心 你没你看起来那么聪明哦
Well, sweetheart, you're dumber than you look.
他现在不在城里 即使他在
Because even if Dad was in town, which he is not…
他也不会中你们的圈套 他精于此道
he wouldn't walk into this. He's too good.
他是很厉害 我也会证明给你看
He is pretty good, I'll give you that.
但你知道吗
But you see…
他有个弱点
he has one weakness.
是什么？
What's that?
你们俩
You.
他小心翼翼的保护着他的孩子们
He lets his guard down around his boys.
让他的情绪干扰了他的判断
Lets his emotions cloud his judgments.
我刚好知道他到城里了
I happen to know he is in town.
而且他会来救你们
And he'll come and try to save you.
我刚好知道他到城里了 他会过来救你们的
I happen to know he is in town.
那个时候daeva会杀了所有人
And then the Daevas will kill everybody…
漂亮的 慢慢的 一地都是
nice and slow and messy.
那我必须得和你说明
Well, I got news for you.
就凭几个影子是杀不了他的
It's gonna take a lot more than some shadow to kill him.
这些daeva就在这个房间里
Oh, the Daevas are in the room here.
你看不到它们
They're invisible.
你唯一能看到只是它们的影子
Their shadows are the only part you can see.
你为什么要这么做 Meg？
Why you doing this, Meg?
你又能获得什么呢
What kind of deal you got worked out here, huh?
和谁呢？
And with who?
我和你一样为着同样的理由
I'm doing this for the same reasons you do what you do.
忠诚
Loyalty.
爱
Love.
就像你对你妈妈 还有杰茜的爱一样
Like the love you have for Mommy. And Jess.
滚回你的地狱里去
Go to hell.
宝贝 我早就在那里了
Baby, l'm already there.
来吧 萨姆
Come on, Sam.
没必要彼此态度那么恶劣
There's no need to be nasty.
我认为我们彼此都知道
I think we both know…
你对我的感觉
how you really feel about me.
你知道吗
You know…
我看到你 在看着我
l saw you watching me…
在房间里换衣服
changing in my apartment.
那让你兴奋 不是吗？
It turned you on, didn't it?
你们两个外面去开个房
Get a room, you two.
我不介意
l didn't mind.
我喜欢你看着我们
I liked that you were watching me.
来吧 萨姆
Come on, Sammy.
我们能找点乐子
You and I can still have a little dirty fun.
你想找乐子？继续啊 来啊
You wanna have fun? Go ahead then.
可我现在有点累
I'm a little tied up right now.
你想转移我的注意力？
Now, were you just trying to distract me.
然后你哥哥可以逃脱？
While your brother cuts free?
不
No.
不是
因为我自己也有刀
It was because I have a knife of my own.
萨姆
Sam.
毁了那个祭坛
Get the altar.
不 不
No. No.
不
No.
我想那些daeva不是那个恶魔
So I guess the Daevas didn't like being bossed around.
我猜也是
I guess not.
嘿 萨姆
Hey, Sam?
下次
Next time.
别再找这样疯狂的女人 好吗？
You wanna get laid find a girl that's not so buckets of crazy, huh?
你为什么不把那些东西留在车里？
Why didn't you just leave that stuff in the car?
我说过 我还是要说一遍
I said it before and I'll say it again.
有总比没好吧
Better safe than sorry.
嘿
Hey.
爸爸
Dad?
嘿 孩子们
Hey, boys.
嘿 萨姆
Hi, Sam.
嘿 爸爸
Hey, Dad.
爸爸 那是个陷阱
Dad, it was a trap.
我不知道 对不起
I didn't know. l'm sorry.
没事 我也想过可能是
It's all right. I thought it might have been.
你在那里吗？
Were you there? Yeah.
我到那里的时候刚好看到她掉下来
I got there just in time to see the girl take the swan dive.
她就是那个凶手 是吗？
She was the bad guy, right?
是的
Yes, sir.
好样的 好的 这没什么奇怪的
Good. Well, it doesn't surprise me.
以前它试图阻止我
It's tried to stop me before.
那个恶魔？
The demon has?
我知道我很接近了 它知道我要杀了它
It knows l'm close. It knows l'm gonna kill it.
不是驱魔或是把它送回地狱
Not just exorcise it or send it back to hell.
真真实实的杀了它
Actually kill it.
怎么样呢？
How?
我正在实施
I'm working on that.
让我们一起 我们能帮忙
Well, let us come with you. We'll help.
不 萨姆
No, Sam.
现在还不行
Not yet.
听着 希望你们能理解
Listen, try to understand…
这个恶魔凶狠狡诈
this demon is a scary son of a bitch.
我不想你们冒险
I don't want you in the crossfire.
更不想你们受伤
I don't want you hurt.
爸爸 你不用担心这个
Dad, you don't have to worry about us.
我当然会
Of course I do.
我是你们的爸爸
I'm your father.
听着 萨姆 上次我们在一起的时候吵得很厉害
Listen, Sammy, last time we were together we had one hell of a fight.
是的
Yes, sir.
再见到你真好
It's good to see you again.
好长的时间啊
It's been a long time.
太长了
Too long.
不
No!
行动起来
Shut your eyes.
这些是影子恶魔
These things are shadow demons.
我们用光来照射
So let's light them up.
爸爸
Dad.
在这里
Over here.
好了 来吧 我们时间不多
All right. Come on. We don't have much time.
当光熄灭 他们会回来
Soon as the flare's out, they'll be back.
等 等
No, wait. Wait.
萨姆 等等
Sam, wait.
爸爸 你不能和我们在一起
Dad, you can't come with us.
什么？你在说什么？
What? What are you talking about?
孩子们 你们要小心
You boys… You're beat to hell.
我们会的
We'll be all right.
迪恩 我们要在一起 我们追踪这些恶魔
Dean, we should stick together.We'll go after this demon together.
萨姆 听我说
Sam, listen to me.
我们在这里差点害死了爸爸
We almost got Dad killed in there.
你不知道吗？他们不会罢休
Don't you understand? They're not gonna stop.
他们会卷土重来
They're gonna try again.
他们会利用我们来抓住爸爸
They're gonna use us to get to him.
我的意思是梅格是对的
I mean, Meg was right.
当爸爸和我们在一起 他要危险得多
Dad's vulnerable when he's with us.
他… 没有我们 他更强壮 不易受伤
He's stronger without us around.
爸爸
Dad.
不
No.
这一切
After everything.
在我们找寻你这么久后 求你不要离开
After all the time we've spent looking for you…Please.
我要加入这场战争
l gotta be a part of this fight.
萨姆 这场战争才刚刚开始
Sammy, this fight is just starting.
我们都有我们各自该面对的
And we are all gonna have a part to play.
相信我 儿子
For now, you gotta trust me, son.
好了 你必须得让我离开
Okay? You gotta let me go.
小心点 孩子们
Be careful, boys.
我们走吧
Come on.